{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_16_BIY0OM",
                "player_5_BIY0OM",
                "player_6_BIY0OM",
                "player_4_BIY0OM",
                "player_7_BIY0OM",
                "player_12_BIY0OM"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                16,
                5,
                6,
                4,
                7,
                12
            ],
            "animation": [
                "liedown",
                "liedown",
                "pick_up",
                "crouch",
                "pick_up",
                "pick_up"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with dark skin, wearing a black fedora, black turtleneck, black pants, and black shoes.",
                "A female soldier wearing green tactical uniform, backpack, and black boots. Hair is tied back. She carries a utility vest and accessories.",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A woman with fair skin, wearing a white and blue shirt, blue pants, dark boots, a gray bandana, and a utility belt with pouches",
                "A bald man with glasses, dark complexion, wearing a black turtleneck, suit, and shoes",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -64396.224,
                    85128.612,
                    -5575.125,
                    0,
                    147.44780611964143,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -64249.02,
                    85173.72,
                    -5572.925,
                    0,
                    -23.260200321905216,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -64148.733,
                    85130.18,
                    -5565.031,
                    0.0,
                    -0.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -64267.691,
                    84870.398,
                    -5560.103,
                    0,
                    75.76725815034806,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    -64474.152,
                    84687.982,
                    -5577.045,
                    0.0,
                    -90.001,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -64634.336,
                    84953.028,
                    -5576.912,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        },
        "drone": {
            "name": [
                "drone_0_BIY0OM"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                0
            ],
            "animation": [
                "none"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "Aerial drone with a black and white frame, dual rotors, and a streamlined design."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -64502.946,
                    84868.143,
                    -5377.642,
                    0,
                    75.65759445380513,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -64792.368,
            84806.241,
            -5571.149
        ],
        "sample_radius": 920.6593684716864
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player",
        "drone"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            -64476.233,
            84164.643,
            -5616.114,
            0,
            83.34075846222818,
            0
        ],
        [
            -64950.652,
            84684.632,
            -5565.099,
            0,
            26.896306298787387,
            0
        ],
        [
            -64106.837,
            85438.087,
            -5562.528,
            0,
            -120.6040306486462,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_man_in_fedora_hat or the_woman_in_floral_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_camo_vest, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_woman_in_camo_vest or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_camo_vest"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_woman_in_floral_shirt or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_floral_shirt"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, White_Drone or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. White_Drone",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. White_Drone"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many human figures are in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many human figures are in the process of holding something?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many human figures are lying down in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many non-human entities, like drones, are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many human figures in the scene are identified as women?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Among all human figures, how many are both bald and wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many human figures in the scene have a light skin color?",
                "answer": "three"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. liedown",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. crouching"
                ],
                "answer": "A. liedown"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the camo vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. liedown",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "B. liedown"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. lying down",
                    "C. holding something",
                    "D. waving"
                ],
                "answer": "C. holding something"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. walking",
                    "C. jumping",
                    "D. waving"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. liedown",
                    "C. holding something",
                    "D. pointing"
                ],
                "answer": "C. holding something"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walking",
                    "B. running",
                    "C. holding something",
                    "D. reading"
                ],
                "answer": "C. holding something"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in floral shirt relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the woman in floral shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-right of"
            }
        }
    }
}